# **DONGJAE LEE**

dongjae.lee@sf.snu.ac.kr • mori1116.github.io/ • github.com/mori1116

#### **SUMMARY**

I am currently a master's student in computer science and engineering. My current research interests include verifying realistic systems, concurrency, and security. I have research experience with the Coq proof assistant, compiler verification, concurrent program verification, and security.

#### **EDUCATION**

# M.S., Computer Science and Engineering

**Expected 02.2024** 

Seoul National University, Seoul, South Korea

# B.S., Physics, Computer Science and Engineering (Double Major)

08.2021

Seoul National University, Seoul, South Korea

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Max Planck Institute for Security and Privacy

03.2023 - 08.2023

Research Intern: Bochum, Germany

- Advised by Cătălin Hriţcu
- · Worked on secure compilation

## **Software Foundations Lab, Seoul National University**

09.2020 - 08.2021

Research Intern: Seoul, South Korea

- · Advised by Chung-Kil Hur
- · Worked on Conditional Contextual Refinement

# **ROK Army (Mandatory Military Service)**

01.2019 - 08.2020

Sergeant: South Korea

# Integrated Quantum Systems Lab, Seoul National University

04.2017 - 08.2017

Research Intern: Seoul, South Korea

- · Advised by Dohun Kim
- Worked on NV center qubits, programming and developing devices for experiments

# **PUBLICATIONS**

# Stuttering for Free

Minki Cho\*, Youngiu Song\*, **Dongjea Lee**, Lennard Gäher, Derek Dreyer.

International Conference on Object-Oriented Programming, Systems, Languages, and Applications (OOPSLA 2023).

# **Fair Operational Semantics**

Dongjae Lee\*, Minki Cho\*, Jinwoo Kim, Soonwon Moon, Youngju Song, Chung-Kil Hur.

Conference on Programming Language Design and Implementation (PLDI 2023).

# **Conditional Contextual Refinement**

Youngju Song, Minki Cho, Dongjae Lee, Chung-Kil Hur, Michael Sammler, Derek Dreyer.

Symposium on Principles of Programming Languages (POPL 2023).

# Sequential Reasoning for Optimizing Compilers under Weak Memory Concurrency

Minki Cho\*, Sung-Hwan Lee\*, **Dongjae Lee**, Chung-Kil Hur, Ori Lahav.

Conference on Programming Language Design and Implementation (PLDI 2022).

### **TALKS**

Fair Operational Semantics

06.2023

PLDI 2023: Orlando, Florida, United States

Overview of Fair Operational Semantics (as a part of introducing Software Foundations Lab)

02.2023

SIGPL Winter School 2023 (The Korean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers): Seoul, South Korea

<sup>\*</sup>equal contribution

# **TEACHING**

(TA) Topics in Programming Languages (Logic in computer science)	09.2023 - 12.2023
by Makoto Tatsuta: Seoul National University, Graduate level course	
(TA) Principles of Programming by Chung-Kil Hur: Seoul National University, Undergraduate level course	09.2022 - 12.2022
(TA) Principles and Practices of Software Development by Chung-Kil Hur: Seoul National University, Undergraduate level course ACTIVITIES	03.2022 - 06.2022

Developing a Coq tutorial for refinement-based verification: https://github.com/mori1116/refinement-tutorial